{
    "id": "561ed140ca7c4a3d9a33be739d72c779",
    "title": "Identify the adverbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c22fa6bd32cf4c0182f6f89545f247ff",
            "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She sings well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Sings is an adverb",
                        "Well is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The coffee is very hot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "The is an adverb",
                        "Very is an adverb",
                        "Hot is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Kiran is an extremely good dancer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Extremely is an adverb",
                        "Good is an adverb",
                        "Dancer is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is too hot today.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Too is an adverb",
                        "Today is an adverb",
                        "Both of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She speaks all foreign languages fluently.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Speaks is an adverb",
                        "All is an adverb",
                        "Fluently is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The child is now happy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Child is an adverb",
                        "Now is an adverb",
                        "Happy is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He learns his lessons very carefully.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Learns is a verb",
                        "His is an adverb",
                        "Very is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I visit my friend daily.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Visit is an adverb",
                        "My friend is an adverb",
                        "Daily is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will return immediately.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Will is an adverb",
                        "Return is an adverb",
                        "Immediately is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hardly recognized my old friend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Hardly is an adverb",
                        "My is an adverb",
                        "Old is an adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}